<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en-US" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:opensearch="http://a9.com/-/spec/opensearch/1.1/" xmlns:s="http://jadedpixel.com/-/spec/shopify">
  <id>https://www.sarmanfashion.com/blogs/news.atom</id>
  <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.sarmanfashion.com/blogs/news"/>
  <link rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" href="https://www.sarmanfashion.com/blogs/news.atom"/>
  <title>Sarman Fashion - Wholesale Clothing Fashion Brand for Men from Canada - News</title>
  <updated>2021-08-04T21:34:52-04:00</updated>
  <author>
    <name>Sarman Fashion - Wholesale Clothing Fashion Brand for Men from Canada</name>
  </author>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.sarmanfashion.com/blogs/news/sarman-clothing-brand-2021-what-happen-and-what-is-new-with-the-brand</id>
    <published>2021-08-04T21:34:52-04:00</published>
    <updated>2021-08-05T21:12:00-04:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.sarmanfashion.com/blogs/news/sarman-clothing-brand-2021-what-happen-and-what-is-new-with-the-brand"/>
    <title>Sarman Clothing Brand 2021, What Happen and What is New With The Brand</title>
    <author>
      <name>Kamo Sarkissian</name>
    </author>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[So here what happen...<p><a class="read-more" href="https://www.sarmanfashion.com/blogs/news/sarman-clothing-brand-2021-what-happen-and-what-is-new-with-the-brand">More</a></p>]]>
    </summary>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p>Hi <strong>Everyone</strong>, it is over a year that we didn't give any news or post about our brand <strong>"SARMAN"!</strong> It is perfect time to describe how Covid had affected our business and lives.</p>
<p><strong>The Business</strong> is as usual, we are growing everyday and pushing as hard as we can. But like most of the people know that apparel business is not that easy, it’s more about how badly you want it<strong>. People</strong> who think it is easy and they can make quick <strong>dollars</strong> it is a completely lie. </p>
<p><strong>There are </strong>people who are asking us for an advice on how to start their own brand. The first thing we <strong>tell them</strong> that if they don't have a good capital for the first <strong>5</strong> years of their business then don't start the business. Well, most of the people get mad when we advice them this strategy because they think we discourage them instead of motivating them. But we prefer to say the way it is  and not put the person on wrong path and give them <strong>wrong hopes.</strong> We are not saying this to eliminate our future <strong>competition</strong> but we giving an advice like we  tell to our own brother or sister who want to start <strong>their business.</strong></p>
<p><strong>So</strong> now let’s talk about the positive side of our business, we start selling and shipping all over the world and not only in Canada. <strong><br></strong></p>
<p>The Biggest <strong>enemy</strong> of Sarman is <strong>Fraud People</strong>. People who try to use other people credit cards and after 2-3 weeks we get charge backs and we lose all money and on top of that the <strong>Banks charge us additional fees of 15$</strong> for it, which is completely <strong>unfair</strong> but what can we do. So for those<strong> who are trying to fraud us</strong> everyday please <strong>STOP!</strong> You are affecting small business that trying to get their name out. Please<strong> think</strong> if someone will do this to you<strong> how will you feel.</strong> Please lets treat each other as <strong>big family</strong>! Plz</p>
<p><strong>Second Big Problem</strong> is influences, lot of people asking us if they can be our <strong>ambassadors</strong> or <strong>influences</strong>. At the beginning, we give lots of chances to almost everyone that asked us. But most of The people are taking there fame for <strong>granted</strong>. They think that they are famous and they can play games. <strong>Mostly</strong> take our clothes and don't do anything, its almost same as <strong>stilling</strong> from us. They should understand that clothes are <strong>not free</strong> and we work for it. We have our family to feed and our community to help and they seal from people like us who wish them well! that <strong>not right!</strong> Making a swipe up for 24 hours won't hurt anyone and no one will <strong>die from it</strong>, but people are <strong>weird</strong>! Most of the time those people have <strong>fake followers</strong> that they bought and they act like they are J<strong>ennifer Lopez</strong> or T<strong>om Cruise</strong>!</p>
<p><strong>COME ON </strong>Guys help a brother, it just a <strong>swipe up</strong>! And <strong>God</strong> is there! one day someone will do the same to to you as well. And when it happen don't ask <strong>why and how</strong>! Most probably you did the same to someone else..</p>
<p>What is <strong>good</strong> is that we are growing slow by slow. We are meeting great <strong>customers</strong> every single day. To be honest our customers are <strong>the best!</strong> We have clients that order just because they want us to <strong>succeed</strong>! They give us also lots of advice's on our<strong> next collections </strong>by giving us comments on how to<strong> improve</strong>! Some models that are pre-sale loyal customers texting us and telling us what would they do to improve the look of it! Most of the time we listen and it ends up being a <strong>top sale</strong> designs. For that we <strong>thank you</strong>.</p>
<p>We also tried to enter a few <strong>stores</strong> to sale our clothes but with Covid most of the stores are suffering now and they don't have cash flow to invest in new products and resell them for us so we are on <strong>our own for now</strong>!</p>
<p>As <strong>business partners</strong> we have great <strong>manufacture</strong> by our side. The Owner name is<strong> Ersin</strong> who is really talented guy and who has lots of potential in fashion and helps us to succeed. He <strong>fall in love</strong> with our Brand name and now even giving us little more time to pay our orders and offering his designs with his touch. He became like <strong>a little causing</strong> you always wanted! lol We promise him 10% of Share holders when we start reaching <strong>100k</strong> sales per month.</p>
<p><strong>Alex next big move</strong> is that he is moving to <strong>Turkey</strong> for few months to create great contents with a nice views! This days Content is <strong>everything</strong>! The risk is high because he is leaving everything behind for<strong> a dream</strong>! We stress a lot because he is giving up on his apartment in <strong>Moscow</strong> and leaving all belonging behind and<strong> starting all over</strong> in another country!</p>
<p><strong>Something We hate</strong> to hear from people! As everyone know in fashion there is lots successful <strong>Gay people </strong>and mostly famous brand owners are<strong> gay</strong> which, we are really proud of it and we love seeing people succeed in fashion domain because they are <strong>passionate</strong>! But what we hate is lots of <strong>people telling us we won't succeed</strong> because we are <strong>not gay man</strong> and that in fashion only gay man succeed! To be honest we have nothing against anyone but when people generalizing it, it <strong>not motivating us</strong>! Our Brand welcome's anyone who love what we are doing! We stand for <strong>freedom</strong> of choice. Everyone must have <strong>equal rights</strong> to there achievements.</p>
<p>We are really<strong> pro life people</strong> and wish all the best to anyone who come our way, (Black, White, Asian, Gay, Muslim, Transgender or even<strong> aliens</strong>) as longer as you see our vision and love what we create we are welcoming you with open arms and <strong>Love</strong>!</p>
<p>With everything happening around the world it is the time we stop all hate and learn back again how to<strong> love one another</strong>!</p>
<p>In The End Love is everything!</p>
<p>Don't forget about our parents who had given everything for our love!</p>
<p> </p>
<p>On That We Wish you all the <strong>best</strong> and we hope we didn't <strong>offend anyone</strong>. If we did please forgive us we didn't mean it! Just telling a story in this short life that we have <strong>been given!</strong></p>
<p> </p>
<p>This Blogs is just a little journey of our life's and our experience in this world!</p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.sarmanfashion.com/blogs/news/our-love-for-our-home-city-montreal-quebec-canada</id>
    <published>2020-10-30T00:12:50-04:00</published>
    <updated>2020-10-30T05:23:38-04:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.sarmanfashion.com/blogs/news/our-love-for-our-home-city-montreal-quebec-canada"/>
    <title>Our Love for our Home City Montreal, Quebec, Canada.</title>
    <author>
      <name>Kamo Sarkissian</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p>We have been in Montreal, Quebec <strong>since 1998</strong> and thinks had change a lot since we arrived. We will say it is people inside of it who change the Vision of the City.</p>
<p>As most of People who came from their homeland to the new country it takes us many years to adapt to new society and most of the time <strong>let’s not lie</strong> we are not happy of the changes and we complain a lot lol. <strong>Yes we do!!!</strong></p>
<p>One thing that make us more and more proud to live in our Home City <strong>Montreal, Quebec, Canada</strong> are the people who live in it. People are extremely passionate of what they do. Yes off course there is the once who stuck in Money world, greediness and sadness but let not talk about them today instead let us tell you wonderful story about <strong>Greatest once</strong>.</p>
<p>When we start our clothing brand we thought we will have hardest time in world to get noticed but it was completely the opposite. <strong>Montreal it is on the rise</strong> of  lots of talented people! We strongly believe that Montreal will be the next <strong>Big thing</strong> because of it differences. It like a<strong> capital of the world</strong> so many different cultures so many things to discover and everyone bring something different, something <strong>Special</strong>.</p>
<p>Why we think <strong>Montreal is The Next Big thing</strong> is because of kindness and in-powering. <strong>Simple google it!</strong> We have more and more bigger influencers, more creators, more rappers and more artists. <strong>Canada</strong> itself is out-coming in all talents by having greatest musicians, hockey player, basketball players and <strong>list goes on</strong>.</p>
<p>All this it's coming from our own experience and by people who we are surrounded by everyday. Sometimes we have to<strong> refuse</strong> some collaboration because of big volume of talents and requests.</p>
<p>We want simply thank all People who are <strong>wearing proudly</strong> our Clothing Brand <strong>SARMAN. </strong>We Served Over 7000 Canadian and American's people as of today and hoping <strong>double it</strong> by the middle of June 2021.</p>
<p>To be honest our <strong>biggest dream</strong> is to out pass all biggest brands out there in the next 10 years. We had give our-self's a goal in 7 years from now on that  "<strong>Adidas Sucks our left nut and Nike Sucks our right nut</strong>". They are too big brands now, they lost their values, it all corporations now, they don't care for anyone of us, it sad but it true. We know you love them but they are not there for you anymore just money.  It time to make <strong>some space for New Generation. </strong></p>
<p>We hope you guys enjoy our little blog.</p>
<p> </p>
<p><span style="text-decoration: underline;"><strong><em>Stay Safe and Love your Family!</em></strong></span></p>
<p> </p>
<p> </p>
<p> </p>
<p> </p>
<p> </p>
<p> </p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.sarmanfashion.com/blogs/news/sarman-canadien-mens-clothing-brand-2020-story</id>
    <published>2020-07-23T16:44:00-04:00</published>
    <updated>2020-07-24T00:12:43-04:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.sarmanfashion.com/blogs/news/sarman-canadien-mens-clothing-brand-2020-story"/>
    <title>Sarman Canadien Men&apos;s Clothing Brand 2020 (Story)</title>
    <author>
      <name>Kamo Sarkissian</name>
    </author>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p>For those who wonder how Sarman Brand started and who we are.</p>
<p>It was actually a really simple and easy start. We follow our dreams, nothing else matters and it was at any cost. When we say at any cost we mean it! Even if we had to end up on the streets with 2 kids and a wife.</p>
<p>The First Step to our big success is to get rid of people who pull us back and find those who have the same passion as us! By doing this you may hurt lots of people but at the same time, you let them free to follow their dreams.</p>
<p>We are located in Montreal, Quebec, Canada but We ship all over Canada and the USA.</p>
<p>Sarman was created from the family name. We use the first 3 letters which are "SAR" and we add "MAN" for the male gender. That how the name SARMAN was created like Frankinchtain.lol</p>
<p>Sarman stands for all those people who fight, breathe, think, eat, and doing sex thinking of there passion nothing else matters. Lots of people scare doing that because of being afraid of losing everything over it. Where we come from we say if you don't risk you don't drink champagne.</p>
<p>Also if you don't do what you love and want then what is your purpose of living?</p>
<p>At the moment as we speak we are only 2 passionate people Kamo and Alex who gave it all every day to succeed and we don't look back not even for a second. Alex, he is my cousin and Model you guys seeing it every day. He is from Russia for all those who have been wondering. Yes he is a good looking guy lol in the family there is always the one who is beautiful and the other one is the smarter one lol</p>
<p>We still far from our goals and dreams but with your love and support, we know that this is just a matter of time. Our own enemy is the time because time flies so fast, sometimes we laugh and wish that there was more hours in a day then 24! lol </p>
<p>We started a clothing brand at the beginning of 2019. Come buy our clothes and wear them proudly because we doing it for you and our families!</p>
<p>P.S. Please forgive us for our English we try our best to describe what we stand for. Thank you</p>
<p>Stay Strong guys! We love you all !!!</p><p><a class="read-more" href="https://www.sarmanfashion.com/blogs/news/sarman-canadien-mens-clothing-brand-2020-story">More</a></p>]]>
    </summary>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p>For those who wonder how Sarman Brand started and who we are.</p>
<p>It was actually a really simple and easy start. We follow our dreams, nothing else matters and it was at any cost. When we say at any cost we mean it! Even if we had to end up on the streets with 2 kids and a wife.</p>
<p>The First Step to our big success is to get rid of people who pull us back and find those who have the same passion as us! By doing this you may hurt lots of people but at the same time, you let them free to follow their dreams.</p>
<p>We are located in Montreal, Quebec, Canada but We ship all over Canada and the USA.</p>
<p>Sarman was created from the family name. We use the first 3 letters which are "SAR" and we add "MAN" for the male gender. That how the name SARMAN was created like Frankinchtain.lol</p>
<p>Sarman stands for all those people who fight, breathe, think, eat, and doing sex thinking of there passion nothing else matters. Lots of people scare doing that because of being afraid of losing everything over it. Where we come from we say if you don't risk you don't drink champagne.</p>
<p>Also if you don't do what you love and want then what is your purpose of living?</p>
<p>At the moment as we speak we are only 2 passionate people Kamo and Alex who gave it all every day to succeed and we don't look back not even for a second. Alex, he is my cousin and Model you guys seeing it every day. He is from Russia for all those who have been wondering. Yes he is a good looking guy lol in the family there is always the one who is beautiful and the other one is the smarter one lol</p>
<p>We still far from our goals and dreams but with your love and support, we know that this is just a matter of time. Our own enemy is the time because time flies so fast, sometimes we laugh and wish that there were more hours in a day then 24! lol </p>
<p>We started a clothing brand at the beginning of 2019. Come buy our clothes and wear them proudly because we doing it for you and our families!</p>
<p>P.S. Please forgive us for our English we try our best to describe what we stand for. Thank you</p>
<p>Stay Strong guys! We love you all !!!</p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
</feed>
